This isn't a raid. It's a reckoning.
Trap House is a action, crime, thriller film directed by Michael Dowse.
An undercover DEA agent and his partner embark on a game of cat and mouse with an audacious, and surprising group of thieves - their own
rebellious teenagers, who have begun robbing from a dangerous cartel, using their parents' tactics and top-secret intel to do it.
Ray Seale, played by Dave Bautista.
Cody Seale, played by Jack Champion.
Deni Matthews, played by Sophia Lillis.
Yvonne Reynolds, played by Whitney Peak.
Andre Washburn, played by Bobby Cannavale.
Natalia Cabrera, played by Kate del Castillo.
Trap House is a 2025 action thriller film directed by Michael Dowse
and written by Gary Scott Thompson and Tom O'Connor.
It stars Dave Bautista, Jack Champion, Sophia Lillis, Tony Dalton, Whitney Peak,
Inde Navarrette, Zaire Adams, Kate del Castillo, and Bobby Cannavale.
The film was released in the United States on
November 14, 2025, by Aura Entertainment.
The tone is intense.